let englishHistory = [];

const englishQuestions = [
    {
        question : 'Choose the option that best completes the gap. While the worshippers closed there eyes in prayers, a theif made _______ with the collection',
        options : ['away', 'up', 'by', 'through'],
        answer :'away',
        duration : 10
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the option that best completes the gap. if you keep playing with this door handle, it will get ____',
        options : ['loose', 'lose', 'loosed', 'losing'],
        answer :'loose',
        duration : 10
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. The man reasoned that there ought to be a limit to sycophancy',
        options : ['there can be no favour beyond a reasonable point', 'syncophants need not talk all the time', 'people should know when not to use flattery', 'sycophants should know when to grant people requests'],
        answer :'people should know when not to use flattery',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the word(s) or phrase(s) which best fills(s) the gap. I whould have been surprised if you ____ the orange',
        options : ['plucked', 'did pluck', 'have plucked', 'had plucked'],
        answer :'have plucked',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the word(s) or phrase(s) which best fills(s) the gap. By the time the plane reaches Harare, it ___ in the air for twelve hours',
        options : ['has been', 'would be', 'would have been', 'should be'],
        answer :'would have been',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the word(s) or phrase(s) which best fills(s) the gap. The patient is suffering from _____',
        options : ['reumatism', 'rheumantism', 'rhuematism', 'rheumatism'],
        answer :'rheumatism',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the word(s) or phrase(s) which best fills(s) the gap. We saw Ifueko _____ an egg on the wall',
        options : ['smashed', 'smash', 'smashing', 'smashes'],
        answer :'smash',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the word(s) or phrase(s) which best fills(s) the gap. Knowledge of figures of speech as well as of idiom and lexical items _____ in this section',
        options : ['is test', 'have been tested', 'are tested', 'were tested'],
        answer :'are tested',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the word(s) or phrase(s) which best fills(s) the gap. The answers to the questions were discussed ____ the students',
        options : ['between', 'by', 'for', 'to'],
        answer :'by',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the word(s) or phrase(s) which best fills(s) the gap. The shipping company advertised for ____ accountants',
        options : ['two young but highly competent Nigerian', 'young but highly competent two Nigerian', 'two Nigerian, young but highly competent', 'highly competent, but young, two Nigerian'],
        answer :'two young but highly competent Nigerian',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the word(s) or phrase(s) which best fills(s) the gap. If it had rained, we would have to postpond the concert. it didnt rain so _____',
        options : ['we won\'t have to', 'we would have had to', 'we wouldn\'t have to', 'we didn\'t have to'],
        answer :'we didn\'t have to',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the word(s) or phrase(s) which best fills(s) the gap. Now, I am used _____ bread without butter',
        options : ['to eat', 'in eating', 'of eating', 'to eating'],
        answer :'to eating',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the option that best completes the gap. we look forward to _____ from you very soon.',
        options : ['Have to', 'Hear', 'Hearing', 'Heard'],
        answer :'Hearing',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the option that best completes the gap. All God\'s prophets were given the great _____ to preach the salvation to people',
        options : ['Commision', 'Commition', 'Comission', 'Commission'],
        answer :'Commission',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the option that best completes the gap. The principal _____ our mobile phones',
        options : ['Seized', 'Ceased', 'Siezed', 'Seased'],
        answer :'Seized',
        duration : 20
    },
    {
        question : 'Choose the option that best completes the gap. You may now ____ with your presentation',
        options : ['Precede', 'Preceed', 'Procede', 'Proceed'],
        answer :'Proceed',
        duration : 20
    },
    
]
